Hello everyone and welcome to English Pod.
My name is Marco.
My name is Katherine
and today we have the
continuation of our series
about giving a presentation.
That's right today
it's part six and on this
occasion we're going
to address the audience.
So we're going to talk to the
audience and explain a couple of things.
Alright so let's take a
listen to today's speech and
we're back in a moment to
talk about what's going on.
Now as we've already discussed there's a
huge untapped market out there both in Asia
and other developing markets and in the
more mature markets for us to push into.
Now of course this
represents an enormous
challenge with enormous
rewards for the winners
but for any new product we need a great
marketing message and marketing campaign.
It needs to be directed
and focused at our target
consumer and needs to be
pitched at exactly the right level.
The question we
must first address is
of course who is our target
consumer and secondly
what do they expect from the
next generation alpha laptop?
Let's first of all tackle
the first question.
Our target consumer
for the X420 is the middle
class white collar worker
with an above average income.
However as we
mentioned before the total
number of computer
owners is expanding rapidly
and we need to broaden
our audience for this product.
For example the X420
is also ideally suited
to a younger student
sector who might use laptops
both for studying and
gaming. There's no doubt that.
Mr. Ford if I could just
interrupt a moment.
You say that the computer
is suitable for students
but you don't think the price of the
X420 is just too much for most students?
Well that's a fair point.
If you don't mind I'd
like to tackle your
question a little bit later
in the Q&A section.
Is that okay? Yes sure.
Okay so as I was saying we
have an exciting campaign
planned for the X420.
Firstly we'll have a
nationwide television
campaign as well as advertising
on radio and also in many
computer publications.
We also intend to. I'm
sorry to stop you Mr.
Ford but do you really think
that a television campaign
is cost effective? I mean how
much is that going to cost?
Well I don't have
the figures to hand
but I'd be happy to discuss
those figures with you
after the presentation.
Okay let me just go on and
talk a little more about
the exciting campaign we
have in store. All right
we're back and now let's
take a look at five keywords
on language takeaway.
Language takeaway. All
right so first up Marco we
have a verb the verb
is to devise. That's right
so we devised a campaign.
Okay so to devise in this
case means to create or
to come up with. That's
right I think in many
movies you will hear that
someone will devise a plan
and to destroy the world
for example. Right or to
devise a scheme so that's
to create or to come up with a
plan or come up with something.
And talking about
the computers he
mentioned a couple of
words that describe it especially
the affordability of
the laptop computer.
Okay so yeah there's this
string of nouns that Mr.
Ford things are very
important relating to the perfect
laptop and in this case
affordability is the first one.
So something that is affordable is something
that you can have the money to buy.
It's not too expensive that's the
adjective affordable. Affordability
means whether or not
something is expensive.
That's right so if you
think of the adjective
affordable the noun would
be affordability so this is
just the way that you can
transform an adjective into a noun.
Right so this is
something that comes
up a lot when we're
talking about buying things
for example Marco I
could say what do you look
for when you're buying
a car. Right so I can say
affordability and you
could also say our next one
which is reliability.
That's right so if you look
for a car you are also
looking for reliability
and this comes from
the adjective reliable.
All right so something is
reliable if you can depend on it.
It means you know in the case of a
laptop or a car it won't break easily.
That's right so a person can
also be reliable you can trust
that person to help
you for example.
Or I could trust that he'll
never be late or never forget
that we have an appointment.
That's exactly right.
Well moving on to
the next part of Mr.
Ford's speech he talked
about the television campaign
and how he really hopes to reach out to a
huge audience with this television advert.
All right so the reason
we've chosen this is
because it's important to
remember this as a phrase
to reach out to. That
means to connect with and
I think your example
of television is a really
great one because television allows people
to reach out to many many many people.
That's right also for example
with internet you are able to
reach out to many
people all over the world.
So to reach out to
is to connect with.
Okay and for our last word when
he was about to show everyone
the TV advert he said that
tonight for the first time
we will unveil the first
of these advertisements.
All right so to unveil
something is actually very
exciting because to
unveil something is to show
it for the very first time.
That's right so maybe
you've seen in car shows
where they have a car
under a big white sheet
and on that night they're
going to unveil the
new model of the I don't
know the Ford car. So
that's what it means to
unveil to take away this veil
and show everyone to unveil.
All right so a lot of good keywords
there when we go back and listen to Mr.
Ford again and when we return
we'll talk about fluency builder.
Now as we've already discussed there's a
huge untapped market out there both in Asia
in other developing markets and in the
more mature markets for us to push into.
Now of course this
represents an enormous
challenge with enormous
rewards for the winners
but for any new product we need a great
marketing message and marketing campaign.
It needs to be directed
and focused at our target
consumer and needs to be
pitched at exactly the right level.
The question we must first address is
of course who is our target consumer and
secondly what do they expect from
the next generation alpha laptop.
Let's first of all tackle
the first question.
Our target consumer for
the X420 is the middle class
white collar worker within
above average income.
However as we mentioned
before the total number
of computer owners is
expanding rapidly and we
need to broaden our
audience for this product.
For example the X420
is also ideally suited to
a younger student sector
who might use laptops
both for studying and
gaming. There's no doubt that.
Mr. Ford if I could just
interrupt a moment.
You say that the
computer is suitable for
students but you don't
think the price of the X420
is just too much for most
students. Well that's a fair point.
If you don't mind
I'd like to tackle
your question a little bit
later in the Q&A section.
Is that okay? Yes sure.
Okay so as I was saying
we have an exciting
campaign planned for the X420.
Firstly we'll have a
nationwide television
campaign as well as
advertising on radio and also
in many computer
publications. We also intend
to. I'm sorry to stop
you Mr. Ford but do you
really think that a television
campaign is cost effective?
I mean how much
is that going to cost?
Well I don't have the
figures to hand but I'd
be happy to discuss
those figures with you
after the presentation.
Okay let me just go on
and talk a little more
about the exciting campaign
we have in store. All
right we're back so now
let's take a look at
these four key phrases
we've picked out for
you today. Fluency Builder.
So in the beginning
Mr. Ford is talking about
this exciting X420 and
he says that you know
he would like to say
that without the help of
each and every one of
you the campaign could not
have been created. So
each and every one of you.
That's right this is
just a phrase where you
emphasize that everyone
helped you or that you
are thanking everyone.
So in a speech you can say
I want to thank each
and every one of you.
So I want to thank everyone
is basically what you're saying.
And it's interesting
because it's kind of like
you're saying every single
person was important.
Right. It's not just like
hey guys thank you it's
like no thank you and
you and you and you.
So each and every one of
you it really emphasizes that
each person has helped.
That's right and it's a
really nice way of for
example thanking someone
saying I want to thank
each and every one of you it
sounds a lot more personal.
Definitely okay and he
also used another very
interesting phrase when he
said I'd like to take my
hat off and really thank
you all for your wonderful
work. So this makes me
think of a person
actually back when people
used to wear hats every
day taking his hat off
and maybe bowing.
Right. This is something that
used to be very polite
because you know when you
meet someone or you want
to thank someone you take
your hat off as a sign
of respect. Well we don't
wear hats anymore so
it seems a little funny
but we still say this I
want to take my hat off
to you Marco that
means I want to thank you.
That's right. So you're
showing respect and you're
also showing admiration
maybe for someone.
So maybe if you meet somebody
who saved someone's life
you would say I really
want to take my hat off
and thank you for the
work that you've done.
Yes you're impressed you
respect that person who
saved that life and you
want to thank them for
their good deed. That's
right. Well moving on when
he continued to talk
about alpha computers and
the marketing efforts
he said there's no doubt
in my mind that we
have a great workforce.
All right so another way
to say this is I definitely
think we have a great
workforce. That's right.
You know maybe not
it's not as interesting right.
So we're making this
more interesting by using
a very colorful phrase
and to say there's no
doubt that you're a
great workforce it's good.
Mm hmm. But there's no
doubt in my mind means
there's there's absolutely
no way that I could doubt this.
I absolutely believe that
you are the best workforce.
Right so and you can
use it with anything.
You can say there's no doubt
in my mind IBM computers
are the best computers
out there for example.
Or there's no doubt in my mind that the
Yankees will win the World Series next year.
That's right okay. So that's
the way that you can use it.
You're basically
telling people that
you are very very sure. Mm
hmm. And what about our
last phrase a very
interesting one when he says
our campaign will really
hammer home the point.
Okay well you can make a point.
You can say listen our
computers are state of the art and
they're the best for your
needs. But to hammer
home the point means to really emphasize
this one important point and to say listen.
You will never forget
this. Okay you will not
forget what I'm going to
say to you. So you really
emphasize it and restate
it. This is something
that can be frustrating
when you're a consumer when
you're watching an
advertisement because you hear
them say this is the best
product. You shouldn't
buy other products. This
is the best product and
they're hammering home the
point. They're repeating this message.
That's right. So
it's a colloquial
phrase that you can use to
really again put your point across.
Okay so a lot of interesting phrases there
when we take a break and let's listen to
our dialogue again
and we'll be back in a bit.
Now as we've already
discussed there's a huge
untapped market out
there both in Asia in other
developing markets and
in the more mature markets
for us to push into. Now
of course this represents
an enormous challenge
with enormous rewards
for the winners. But for
any new product we need
a great marketing message
and marketing campaign.
It needs to be directed
and focused at our target
consumer and needs
to be pitched at exactly
the right level. The
question we must first
address is of course who
is our target consumer and
secondly what do they expect from
the next generation alpha laptop?
Let's first of all tackle
the first question.
Our target consumer for the X420
is the middle class
white collar worker within
above average income.
However as we mentioned
before the total number
of computer owners is
expanding rapidly and we
need to broaden our audience
for this product. For
example the X420 is also
ideally suited to a
younger student sector who
might use laptops both
for studying and gaming.
There's no doubt that.
Mr. Ford if I could just
interrupt a moment you
say that the computer is
suitable for students but
you don't think the price
of the X420 is just too
much for most students?
Well that's a fair point.
If you don't mind I'd
like to tackle your
question a little bit later in
the Q&A section. Is
that okay? Yes sure.
Okay so as I was saying we
have an exciting campaign
planned for the X420.
Firstly we'll have a nationwide
television campaign
as well as advertising on
radio and also in many
computer publications.
We also intend to. I'm
sorry to stop you Mr.
Ford but do you really think that a
television campaign is cost effective?
I mean how much
is that going to cost?
Well I don't have the
figures to hand but
I'd be happy to discuss
those figures with you
after the presentation.
Okay let me just go on
and talk a little more
about the exciting campaign
we have in store. All
right so this was part
six of our presentation
series. We still have
four more lessons to
go all about this and
they're going to get a
little bit more complicated
and we're going to
continue talking and the next
couple of lessons are
actually answering questions
from the public and
many things like this.
Yeah I think they're really
useful because sometimes you
prepare your presentation
you feel really good
about it but those
questions at the end can be
scary because you don't
really know how to answer
a question properly
in English or you don't
know how to anticipate
a question that you might
get from the crowd. So
those are things that we
would like to talk about in
the next couple of episodes.
That's right and remember
that these phrases
and how you see him
presenting this laptop computer.
You can still take a
lot of the words, a lot
of the vocab, a lot of the
phrases and kind of put
it into your speech
or your presentation.
You're going to
sound great. Absolutely.
State of the art, save that one
but that's about it for us here
today at English. Probably
hope you've enjoyed this
lesson and we'll see you
next time. All right bye.